[Music]
to enjoy the future in perfect health
that's what everyone
wants while you hope for the best it's
better to face the future prepared for
when an illness or accident hits
you and the best time to prepare for
health problems is when you are
well because once you become ill your
options become
limited you you can have a brighter
future with sun life's health and
excident insurance
products the primary forms of health and
excident insurance products are critical
illness Hospital income and accident
Insurance critical illness
Insurance ask yourself are you covered
when life altering critical illness hits
you will your Financial Health still be
on track if you need to spend as much as
a million pesos for your hospital
expenses
critical illness insurance is designed
to pay the expenses associated with life
altering
illnesses if you are diagnosed with a
certain critical illness covered by our
policy you will receive a lumpsum cash
payment after the set time
period so you can focus on getting well
and not on your
finances Hospital income
Insurance are you adequately covered if
you suddenly get hospitalized for a
period of time Hospital income Insurance
can help cushion the impact of loss of
income due to
hospitalization with daily income
replacement it can help absorb the cost
of travel to and from the hospital for
treatment for rehabilitation and
recovery and allow you to focus on your
recovery so you can get back on your
feet and face the future with a
smile accident
insurance if you get into an accident
are you ready to face the costs related
to it even if we try our best to avoid
accidents the fact is they can
happen accident Insurance can help cover
the expenses associated with such
unforeseen
events it can provide you Financial
Resources in the incidents of accident
covered by your
policy so you have a worry-free time to
heal and completely
recover health and accident
Insurance to know more about Sun life's
health and exellent insurance products
talk to a sunlife adviser
today or visit sunlife.com pH
[Music]